Pioneers have always been
met with ridicule after Mr.
Gentlemen, were scientists.
As a month,
they tested observable phenomena.
And let me see.
Your thesis is that voices of the dead
can be heard through the new London
Telephone network.
Do I have that right, Mr.
Hay? Dr. Haig.
But may I ask,
how many of these voices you
yourself have discerned
through the static interference?
No, Mummy not rung lately.
We are not without sympathy for your loss.
My own dear
mother passed away just a year ago.
But even so,
we are to officially inform you
that as of this moment,
you are no longer a member of Her
Majesty's Royal Medical Society.
Struck off.
Wasn't that a telephone?
I. Hello.
Very much so.
Patient.
Who should grant me a little grace.
Just a whisper.
It's just a song.
We always loved our songs.
And have
you rather
them.
Out? Why does Emily always get flowers.
For. Murder?
Still, the two of.
Me, Kirby.
We are not common thieves.
Are you sure it's even this place?
So many pompous
fish on the side of the city.
Where else
are they going? To put someone like a.
Dump them in the river.
I am gonna need some sleep.
Sometimes when I'm digging these graves,
I think maybe I'm just annoyed
in underneath the corpse.
That's nice.
Tell me more.
Finally
got him.
Drilled straight through the bloody floor.
That's how we see Melody.
Okay.
In front of all the fucking building
that cross shot
right
now. Can you direct you to the women's
barracks,
or am I a little early for this room?
There'll be an investigation.
So you can't take anything.
This is when
the touched
base is a revenge formality.
No. They won't stop
until they've shook
London into the ground.
She's got no one now.
And you.
Do nothing.
Right?
I just.
So we know the last place Mandy was seen
around hanging.
We know she was dressed.
As a female, also deceased.
According to your research.
I wager the colonel's still with us,
and we can offer a reward.
Someone must have seen him on the streets.
Fed while in mire or moaning
about our mismanagement of young men.
Remind me it was the officer
in charge of that again.
I'll just call him up.
Should I tell him you went along the wrong
bloody woman?
She wasn't even. Touched. It's the truth.
No one wants to hear it.
The chance.
You know,
if you don't tell the public about melody.
What are you going to do?
Go down Fleet Street.
You set one gelato in the direction
of those newspaper markets Monday.
And I will personally make sure that
every last drop of this side of Hadrian's
fucking wall knows
what kind of man you are.
The company you search out after dark.
Or your gentleman friends.
I like to do my research, you know.
It's good to know you're working with.
But there'll be no more special privileges
on my watch.
You try and push through on this.
Be five years hard
labor and public disgrace.
I don't think
many people would be interested
in your little story, then, would I Not?
The best place for your sort
prison. So
I'll just really do this.
And I.
Tightening of the touch detail. Yeah.
And to be
well,
go mine.
This is true.
Mr. Dan.
You did it.
But did it.
How was the recon?
Have no idea what we were doing there.
But they've tripled in numbers
since yesterday.
Grand is the same.
It wasn't your fault.
Melody didn't want to be saved.
It was a grave error.
Do you know?
It just made me think of a soul
wandering through the streets of London
for eternity.
All those people just electrocuted.
They did come to watch her hanged.
Harriet said some of them brought picnics.
But you would have thought
that if anyone could have spotted
those powerlines, it should have been me.
She ran them through here. Look.
So obvious.
Stop going over it.
Is that how
you dealt with it when you were a soldier?
Well,
the death is just something going a bit.
I had a job to do.
Shall we make a start on our man?
You're going to have that meeting first.
You know the meeting where you tell
everyone about the future planting.
What's actually.
Going on?
There's no time limit.
I've lived through this before, remember?
Earthquakes are just the starting gun.
It's a matter of days
before the glenfinnan match.
You have an hour to spare now.
You have to be down there with it
when it happens in case
it needs protection or transport or.
I don't fucking know what it'll need.
A map.
The ship.
Well, whatever it needs us, I can help.
You owe them the truth.
We can't do this by committee.
You know what
it'll be like hiding bloody cats.
No one can agree on anything.
I'm sorry.
It's just so much easier to get on
with things when it's you and me.
Oh, yeah? Yes.
We have the body of that thing right here.
It could be the
answer to who's down there.
Come on, then.
Let's make that start.
Thank you.
Amal is the spirit of a soldier from
the future in the body of a drowned baker.
And she's come here
to tell you all about an alien. Underland.
And who gave you all your magical powers?
Got you.
After a bit of a start, right.
Came out of that cave with a clear mission
to help the LNP and be ready to defend it.
Well, thank you for your time.
Penance and I have some ideas.
What did it tell you?
GALANTI Don't really speak well.
I show you things in your mind.
Okay,
so what things did this one show you?
Just fragments.
Nothing coherent.
I thought it sang Mary song.
That's what Michael translated.
So if I've got this right,
the Galaxy uses its psychic tentacles
to suck out your brain.
Not that kind of alien.
Can you prove it from the future?
How would I do that?
You could tell us what's gonna happen
tomorrow, next week.
The queen dies quite soon.
I don't have my formal debut regret.
It doesn't die.
I mean, does die. Everyone die.
But you didn't, apparently.
So what's the plan?
I mean, I know
there must be a plan, right?
This is the thing you just had us.
Look,
yesterday we went down to the cave,
some of us, anyway.
And it was a shit show.
I only just escaped those human robot
things.
Shock troops.
Oh, that is a good one.
If we go back in blind,
we'll be slaughtered.
Or was there a patch down there?
More like the living dead than people.
Whoever's running this operation
hates us as much as they do the GALANTI.
And as for the shock troops. Yes.
That part of the plan is already underway.
No idea who these people are.
They might even be someone
from the future.
Hitched a ride like me.
Is that what the Clancy showed you?
Like I said, not particularly coherent.
Anyway, penance will work on weapons.
No, not weapons.
Nonviolent objects of confusion
and defense.
And I will continue
drawing up our rescue strategy.
You do have resources here, you know.
What will the alien do when it come out?
What it was supposed to do
in the first place.
Unite humanity.
Oh, that sounds nice and easy. Look.
Best case
scenario, it's going to save the world.
Which were
you said save the world?
That's right.
Because I don't know about any future
of the world outside
this place is on fire.
He said best case scenario.
What's worst case?
It turns the world.
Apart and we all die. Why?
What's going on?
I don't know.
What happened. What was the target thing?
It said flashbacks.
I thought they started.
We came and didn't.
Didn't everything go forward?
Instant Stanley?
Not anyway.
Wasn't the same as before, though.
I sort myself out. All on your own.
Just like always, huh?
My reaction
was, Oh,
okay.
I've heard the soldiers before.
Look at me.
But an exhaustion doesn't go away.
I ignored.
My experience.
That's exactly how it goes away.
I know what I mean. Now you know what?
You want to leave him.
You have no idea
what.
Oh, sorry to interrupt.
Look,
I've done the fucking meeting that we.
Please start.
Fuck,
Tidy up and never leave the things
and the people.
No, not that 16th century fucking Dell.
Jesus Woogie.
You got. This place is an absolute state.
Lucky that I'm here to help them.
No, I prefer not to look at it.
Does that.
Thank you very much.
That the river well sorted out.
This is.
So. I very much doubt you actually remove
my name from those papers.
Don't worry.
Pretty little head about all.
That very much in the. Process. Oh, Jesus.
Then I've got a bleeding.
Ear and a fractured rift. You've been
sleeping.
What?
Tell me everything.
Actually, that is one.
Here I am.
Oh, I do need to tell you something.
And I'm only telling you
because I'm really,
you know, my best friend and I.
So who.
Have you met somebody?
Yes, actually,
I suppose that is part of it was. Is.
I wouldn't want to say.
Oh, secretly delicious.
That you have some advice.
So what went wrong?
Well. Well, I know what I would say.
Yes, please.
I would say
maybe. Woman, I am.
August has been live.
Yes, I am a man in my own right.
A man with a with a bleeding ear and a.
Fractured with a fighting man.
Independent, brave.
Choosing whichever path to adventure
I damn well one.
Of course. You mustn't say any of that.
Oh. Oh, yes. There.
No, he just be your real charming,
awkward self.
Who ask? Well,
that's. That's. That's just it.
You listen my real self.
I was trying to
please do something
about these fucking channels.
There must be some sort of minister
or something.
Somehow I struggle
to see the cream of London decided
to burn out for the sacking.
Honorable, It's a big trip for next to a.
Fucking chamber, Pops.
Bull. No, no,
I really don't think the hell's the time.
And actually, as the
the official proprietor.
If yesterday's grotesque
events have taught me anything, it is
a London needs a fucking party.
So it's right with you.
Orgy might intend to throw a festival.
So extraordinary, so transcendent.
It will pass into legend
and all this gossip.
This will be obliterated. Erased.
You do realize that
the ceremonies
is just a sex club for rich people?
It is not just a sex club.
It is a fucking phenomenal.
Mrs. Beecham should have told you
this door is to remain.
Sorry, my Lord, I. I didn't. Intend to
apologize for the.
Maid First. I.
It's time to go shooting
with all of London up in arms.
Last bit of pheasant
you brought back, though.
Tell Roberts to take that horse
to the lower field. Mr..
His horse always been a spirited creature.
I think it can sense the tremors.
If I was a superstitious woman,
I'd say they were a sign
of something.
Messages from the heavens.
I'd have thought by now
you would have realized that
if there is a God,
he's an Englishman.
He has no interest in declaring
his intentions.
He'll come back for you.
The fucking late night free time
checking aloneness.
Since when do you ever throw in the towel?
Fuck you, Opportunists.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What did you say.
To. Me?
All right,
I had.
You scribbling away for
nimble jokes.
Tales of the touched newspapermen
going to be given their
it to these cities on fire,
and you're spinning stories.
Someone should only role model
for a touch kid
on the street is humanity.
I'd rather they out of fire wielding
Amazonian princess.
Is that what you think my family's from?
Why would she kill herself? So Melody
and all those people she took with her,
was it cause swell and hypocrite.
So why did you work for her?
Let's start with that.
Well,
there was the money.
Nah, I don't know.
She just had something about
the end of the day.
We were just puppets very, you know,
wind up toys with the time.
My kind of later.
Is that what you came
here for, then? A leader.
Don't strike me as the following time.
I'm just passing through.
I never like to stay away from.
Would do this to a movie.
Who could do this?
That's what I want to know.
Look at him.
Time that's been taken. The design.
I just hope the artists left
some kind of signature.
Could be the first step towards whoever's
got the calamity under armed guard.
Jimmy here can get some justice
for what was done to him.
Jimmy.
After my Uncle Jim, what happened to.
You know, Look, I'm just missing.
How does that replaces the nervous system?
I thought to be electrical with a circle
of charge to make the last so long.
Nice to see you enjoying your work.
Oh, no, no,
it is horrible. I just
never seen this kind of science before.
This isn't science.
This is evil.
What's that?
Was that connected to?
I think that the nerves, not the wiring.
It looks like some sort of casing.
It's that.
Just thump.
Oh, yes.
The letters
Chinese
ten Penfield Clockmaker.
You need to come with us.
No trouble in Limehouse
these days. We're all ready for trouble.
Mrs. Czerny, please to.
I only speak a few words of Chinese badly.
I know.
Not that, but in.
My opinion, that.
It's trespassing.
So today I want to go out.
Well, children are let go.
Sugar Catholics.
You go.
From high to.
Malia.
Oh, no.
We'll be walking targets
like they're wearing those.
Mrs. True and I,
we were on a bit of a mission, so.
I'm going
on about about that with the the cave.
And I wanted to apologize have
and also
also not have not apologize actually,
because I'm I'm my own man.
I'm I'm a fighter and I'm a
I just I'm going to pull them
full of pollen.
I'm going to follow my own path,
whatever way that takes me.
Amalia. What? Just wait.
Citizens
embarrassing.
To tell you what, though,
all this focus on the glancy.
There's no one out there anymore.
Doing what?
Mrs. True And Lucy, you still.
Looking out for the likes of us?
Who knows? There's more.
Don't envy them today.
My friends
blessed me, Made me
Brother used to come here when he was.
Scott was
big around find Also.
I never knew you had a family.
What do you think?
I just walked up here one day.
Perhaps I like gloomy at work and
thought the way of the summoning rain.
That woman,
every boy or that journalist among
you was in the station.
She was out.
He was laughing again, whispering,
You're jealous.
Did you know every man before?
Have What's she saying to you?
What did she say?
Let me see.
She said that
she thought you wasted in your job.
You said that?
She said that the longer you spend that
rotten police force of yours, the further
you off from ever being a man
you're meant to be.
Carmine, Is not that,
you know, thing about you.
Well,
I sense that you're going to tell me.
Yeah.
The thing about you
is you got to own the bluebloods,
the money, the parties that you wear it
well, but I think underneath
you despise it.
I don't think you want none of it.
And I suppose
you're going to tell me what it is
that I want, not.
Not our Colonel Kleinman.
I wonder
if we go.
I know that
will not get me in your little club.
Get me some of that charm.
She saw her.
She told me
to keep an eye on you.
Whether you like it or not.
Everybody needs a friend, Frank.
I do.
What?
Ordinarily, a guest waits
for an invitation before paying a visit.
Perhaps you should tell that to Mrs.
Amalia. True.
After all, I didn't invite her
to our little excavation site.
Did you?
And your dance?
You came all the same.
This is true.
What was she doing?
Talking to the creature, apparently
decapitating a few of my guards.
The thing. The communicating.
I think she upset it.
All these earthquakes.
You think the monster is responsible
for the tremors?
Is there any way that she could have
discovered my involvement?
Anything in the case? Think.
You know, it's been raised before,
but I question Mrs.
True's credentials.
She doesn't seem like a baker to me.
And I'm beginning to wonder if your two
little projects may no longer be quite
compatible.
Rehabilitate has always been designed
to go hand in hand with a cure.
But what if society were to find out
about our sideline,
our little cerebral
forays?
Medical breakthroughs have always
required human trials.
I will take care of Amalia. True.
And when the creature is dead,
she and her kind will all be released
from that purgatorial affliction.
Well, truthfully, if it's even taken
form in there, we don't know
quite what effect killing
the creature might have.
Our doubts are traitors, are they not?
But with you beside me,
Lavinia,
I find I the resolve itself.
Much farther to.
The clockmaker.
Not far.
Okay. I didn't mean all that.
The cave.
You know
you are allowed to make your own choices.
I Just thought
if I could find the Clan of Faith
and it might let you show me.
Tell me what it turns out.
The thought of wearing one of these things
a lot more frightening than going off
to face
the might of Her Majesty's armed forces.
Would you? Would you do the honors?
You know, it's not the best day
to be wearing one of those things.
It doesn't matter
what's right.
Sorry. Some
the the birds today,
I think losing his erection.
Because of the tremors.
Something the bookseller's,
the witchcraft and powers.
Who These are an affront to God
and he ever shall London
such songs of pleasure
tracking are very powerful with the stars.
You have to travel
Shouldn't stay.
Filling the streets with fire and blood.
What about you, brothers and sisters?
Will you not. Answer his call?
Will you awaken to his love
for, you know, rise on young
love?
That's what
I'll fucking wait.
Yeah.
You've got a reckoning coming. I
This is the piece
we found.
You recognize it?
It is a kissing
from one of our carriage clocks.
That is a number in the mark
of a foreign legion jingle on.
We will find a buyer for you
in much trouble with these men.
They say the city belongs to them.
None of the touch can stay in Chinatown
at the same time.
The time
someone is giving the purest names.
You know,
for if.
She's from the address.
That's the way
to. Get.
Locked.
You know the phrasing.
She Italian? What's she saying?
She's not Italian.
She's touched to
speak again.
I What?
I said speak for
my friends.
It is. Because you, by God, touch.
I know I've seen this. You.
There's the curse on us.
And you've taken you take it.
You turn everything back there.
Come on.
You offer to.
Help. Now
Wrath.
You read me?
Run life.
What are you doing in your eyes?
Fucking blinded me.
You catch me in the unmentionable
vagina is not unmentionable Penance.
We've been through this before. Oh.
This is true.
This is death.
How did you get here?
What dangerous does it matter?
We put.
Jimmy
to hate.
Darling, Who is this?
This your calling?
Speak to.
That accent.
Am I wrong?
It's Canadian.
Originally,
I like me.
How did you ever stop believing this was
you on the street and fuck are you,
my dear?
Did you think you were the.
Only one who arranged a ride.
Hello?
How was the coffee
fire?
Getting to my prayer
and the day of my trip.
Click on you for that.
No, not the praying. In these.
Seems fine to me.
Yeah, exactly. How.
How big is the ocean? And over.
Let me call you back.
That's a really good question.
Tell me if you had not.
You ready?
And this tax season,
we all have a lot going on.
I can't, man.
Luckily, TaxACT has a free expert
help you need
so you can get back to the things
that matter most.
File for less and get more Tax Act
and see Marvel Studios, Ant-Man
and the WASP Quantumania only in theaters.
In Northeastern has empowered me to.
Make an impact in environmental policy,
even though I'm still in classes
and haven't graduated yet at Northeastern,
my job isn't just to teach.
It's to connect our graduate students
to real opportunities.
I'm not only N.A., I'm an alumni.
My connection to Northeastern
is oftentimes and often it would be a.
Whatever your child's dreams may be.
Come on can help them come through.
Our math and reading program works.
Thanks to the.
Power of practice, regular practice
delivers mastery and confidence
so your child can retire and achieve more.
Encourage your child
to imagine the very brightest future
and let human help make it happen.
Why would you not tell me
about these rankings
to come?
I'm losing my fucking mind.
I'm breaking up into little pieces.
What have the L.A.
Times out, Major?
Disappear
so far?
Alexis Navy, you listen to me
right now.
You have a name to our enemy.
We have a strange old lady
from the future.
On the other end of a telephone line.
We have an alien under threat.
We have a mission to save the world.
So I will not hear one more word from you
about disappearing
or breaking up or getting up.
Do you want to stop me, soldier?
Get on your fucking feet
and get back to work.
Three
to. Oh,
hello.
Isn't going to stop.
Oh, he will.
Yes, I.
Will.
They done?
We can't let you stand.
Na, na na
na na na
na na na.
Mother.
Oh, my lord.
All along.
Na you.